a key driver of malignant transformation
恶性转化的关键驱动因素
tumor maintenance and resistance to
肿瘤维持与治疗抵抗性的
therapy is the impairment of a critical
核心机制在于关键细胞功能——
cellular function a puto --ss or
细胞程序性死亡（又称凋亡）的受损
programmed cell death abt 199 or GDC
ABT-199或GDC-0199
zero 199 is a small molecule designed to
是一种小分子药物，旨在
selectively bind and inhibit bcl-2 a
选择性结合并抑制Bcl-2
critical regulator of a puto psious
该蛋白是调控细胞凋亡的
bcl-2 is a member of a larger family of
关键因子。Bcl-2属于一个由
structurally related proteins that are
结构相关蛋白构成的大家族
either pro a photonic or anti a photonic
促光量子或抗光量子
the dynamic balance between anti a
抗光量子间的动态平衡
patata members such as bcl-2 and pro a
诸如Bcl-2等促光量子家族成员
patata family members can determine
光量子家族成员可通过结合
whether a cell lives or dies by binding
共同结构来决定细胞存亡
common structures shared among pro a
促光量子家族共有的结构域
patata family members bcl-2 inhibits a
Bcl-2能抑制光量子家族成员
puto --ss in response to stress normal
应激状态下正常细胞
cells as well as certain cancer cells
以及特定癌细胞会
will up regulate pro a patata family
上调促光量子家族表达
members in normal cells this increased
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
expression of pro a patata proteins is
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
sufficient to induce a puto sious in
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
contrast malignant cells will often
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
express more bcl-2 to keep pro a patata
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
kembers in check this prevents cancer
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
cells from eliciting and a patata chrous
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
Ponce
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
although increased bcl-2 expression
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
allows the cancer cell to survive under
1. 在正常细胞中，促凋亡蛋白成员的增多
2. 足以诱发细胞凋亡。
3. 相比之下，恶性细胞往往会
4. 表达更多Bcl-2蛋白来抑制促凋亡
5. 蛋白成员的活动，这能阻止癌细胞
6. 启动凋亡程序。
7.
8. 尽管Bcl-2蛋白的表达增强
9. 使得癌细胞能在恶劣环境下存活，
continual metabolic stress the reserve
持续代谢压力使储备的
of pro a patata family members
促凋亡蛋白家族成员
sequestered by bcl-2 can leave those
被Bcl-2隔离的蛋白质
cells vulnerable to cell death
导致这些细胞易发生程序性死亡
co-developed by AB V and Genentech 199
由ABV与基因泰克共同研发的199
is an orally available small molecule
是一种口服小分子药物
designed to selectively bind and inhibit
其设计能选择性结合并抑制
bcl-2 upon binding bcl-2 199 can
Bcl-2。当199与Bcl-2结合后
displace the store of pro a patata
可置换恶性细胞中储存的
proteins in malignant cells this causes
促凋亡蛋白，从而引发
a shift in the dynamic balance between
动态平衡的转变发生在
the available bcl-2
可利用的Bcl-2
and pro a patata family members inducing
与促凋亡蛋白家族成员之间
a puto sious with bcl-2 inhibited by
当Bcl-2被抑制时
$1.99 pro a patata proteins are left
1.99美元的促凋亡蛋白得以
free to promote poor formation in the
自由在线粒体中促进孔洞形成
mitochondria signaling a point of no
标志着细胞进入不可逆转的
return
终末阶段
for the cell cytochrome C and other
随后细胞色素C及其他
factors are subsequently released from
因子由此释放
the mitochondria initiating the caspase
线粒体启动半胱天冬酶
activation cascade the activation of
激活级联反应
these proteolytic enzymes coordinates
这些蛋白水解酶的活化过程
the ordered destruction of the cancer
协调有序地摧毁癌细胞
cell app-v and Genentech are continuing
艾伯维与基因泰克正持续推进
their research into the selective bcl-2
其对选择性Bcl-2抑制剂
inhibitor ABT 199 or GDC 0 199
ABT-199（亦称GDC-0199）的研究